hostdare.com 2019-05-04

# Hosting Plan

### Privacy Policy

By using HostDare’s ("Hostdare", "our", "us" or "we") products and services, you ("you", "your", "Client" or "Customer") agree to comply with our policies. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you, what we do with the information, and our information security practices. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact support@hostdare.com 

### Information

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to. If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your account and services. When you visit our website we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our website that you view. We may tie this information to personally identifiable information we have about you. We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our website. See “What is a Cookie?” below. If we send you an e-mail, we may include a tracking code that will allow us to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed. 

### Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows: 

  * For payment purposes and to provide customer support. 
  * For fraud checking, reporting, and other screening methods to verify information submitted to us. 
  * For IP usage reporting to ARIN. 
  * To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt out of future e-mails at any time by following the instructions included in the e-mail.
  * To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and website visits to help us improve or target our website and customize your visit. 

We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than: a law enforcement or regulatory agency as requested via subpoena; a person or company who acquires our business; third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential; as otherwise needed to protect or enforce the rights of others. We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists. 

### Information

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to. If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your account and services. When you visit our website we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our website that you view. We may tie this information to personally identifiable information we have about you. We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our website. See “What is a Cookie?” below. If we send you an e-mail, we may include a tracking code that will allow us to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed.
